["Mr. Tailor" playing] ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ In the world's mess ♪
[Olga, in English] Hello. Friend?
I thought of something
we can make money from.
[Charmi] Olga is an actress.
She looks familiar to me.
Abot-Kamay na Pangarap.
Yes, she was an extra there.
[T-Bak] From the start,
- you should've gone for Karla instead!
- [Billy] Exactly!
- Won't Cathy get mad at you?
- Don't worry about that.
[Gavin, in English] Where are we going?
That's my mom.
[Olga] A hundred thousand is nothing
compared to what we'll earn today.
[Ibyang] Mama, is that you?
[in English] Of course,
my darling. [chuckles]
[in English] I'm quite busy right now.
Maybe she's just in character.
[Olga] My ex left that after
he dumped me for another woman.
[Charmi] Only four exist.
- [Olga, in English] Yes.
- Three are in museums.
[man, in English] It's already sold.
[Atoy, in Visayan] Is the Mayor in there?
Can I tell him something?
[security guard] Do you not have
an appointment with him?
[security guard, in Visayan]
I'm sorry, sir,
but we have strict rules here.
The Mayor's receiving death threats.
[man, in English] Oh, it's fake!
[in English] I got scammed!
[in English] Mama?
[Ibyang] Mama scammed the man,
that's why he chased her.
PREVIOUSLY
[grunts and groans]
- Ouch!
- [Olga] Fool!
I'm just helping you.
[Olga] Get out of here!
[man, in English] Maybe it's her!
Stop her!
[Emerson, in English] My love!
♪ Fix it ♪
- Oh, oh.
- My love, don't leave me!
Stay here!
- Don't go.
- [man, in English] Where's the girl?
[security guard] That woman is a thief!
- [security guard] Where did she go?
- [Emerson] A thief? Eh--
- [Emerson] Yes, she stole my heart.
- Where did she go?
Over there! I hope she comes back.
- Find the bag!
- [in English] How about my money?!
- [man, in English] Where is it?!
- [Emerson] I don't know.
I don't know what money
you're talking about--
Sir, is this your bag?
That's her bag.
Wait, that's her bag.
[man, in English] My money is here.
I don't know. I just saw it here.
[in English] My money is here.
Wow! Oh, good thing. It's in her bag.
[barangay police] Just explain
at the community hall.
- [Emerson] Huh? Why should I go?
- [barangay police] Come with us!
- [overlapping chatter]
- Stop pretending.
You're an accomplice of the woman scammer!
- I'm not--
- Come with us!
I just saw her today!
- You're an accomplice!
- No, I'm not!
No, wait, my love!
- [clamoring]
- [action music playing]
[music fades]
[in English] Are you sure
we are in the right place?
[in English] Our intel told us
that the decoder of this town
is the mayor's niece.
[in English] So, she might be here.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] This is the man who broke
into the ambassador's office.
[in English] He might be here too.
[in English] Take a good look at him.
[in English] But be careful.
[in English] This man has many faces
and can be very dangerous.
[music fades]
[in Visayan] Oh,
the secretary of the mayor said
to wait for their message
before we go to their house.
I think someone else is performing.
[performer 2, in Visayan] How about Jun?
[in Visayan] I even brought his costume.
[in Visayan] He abandoned us.
[performer 1, in Visayan] Okay.
This is what we shall do.
[in Visayan] Let's just practice
even if it's just the six of us.
[performer 2, in Visayan] Okay! Let's go!
[in Visayan] So our efforts
won't be in vain.
[suspicious music playing]
[performer 1, in Visayan]
There's a vacant space there.
[performer 3, in Visayan] Drinks, please.
[performer 1, in Visayan] There!
We can practice here.
[Atoy] Boss, here's my payment.
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
Karla, have you spoken to Brother Atoy
after he found out everything?
Not yet, he's not here. He's on a mission.
Thank you, by the way.
Why are you thanking me?
We're the ones bothering you.
No reason. I'm just happy today.
[in English] You don't understand.
No, really.
Be straight with me.
I've been weirded out by you.
You keep smiling,
and you're spending time with us.
- Gavin, are you sick?
- [Gavin chuckles]
[sentimental music playing]
No, I'm not sick.
But you know, what you're doing now
made me realize
I don't really like Cathy.
Then who?
[music fades]
- Who--
- [Cita] Karla.
[unsettling music playing]
Young man, you shouldn't be coming here.
Didn't Atoy forbid you from doing so?
I'll go now.
Mom, why are you like that to Gavin?
Karla, let me remind you.
He's Red Regalia's son.
[Cita] He's the one
who killed your father.
He already clashed with Atoy.
What if his father sent him to snoop here?
To get back at Atoy.
Don't be swayed by his smiles and charm,
even if he's your friend.
Remember. He's a Regalia.
They're bad people.
And in the end,
he'll still choose his family.
[music fades]
Hey, Olga.
So? Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
I'm fine.
I hadn't gone far
when I heard the shouting.
I thought something happened to you!
Are you okay?!
‪No.
The watch was immediately exposed as fake.
I hadn't even left yet.
Ha? Hmm.
No, no. It's fine.
What's important is you
and the money are safe.
[pensive music playing]
Oh?
I thought I could escape.
But…
that fool bumped into me.
The money was left inside the bag.
Oh.
For real?
Olga!
[grunts]
[music fades]
[car door closes]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[music fades]
Ibyang is changing
her clothes in the room.
She already told me
what happened at the mall.
Did you see her mom?
But Ibyang seems sure that she saw her.
[Karla] Brother!
I thought you'd follow.
- You didn't come.
- I was there.
I came, but I ended up
at the barangay hall because
I was accused of being an accomplice
of that woman scammer.
Unbelievable.
The one who ran from the mall?
Yes, the one who
sold the fake watch.
We were at the mall when she got exposed!
- [Emerson] Oh?
- But I didn't see her face.
So, what does she look like?
She's beautiful, sexy, looks rich.
[pensive music playing]
- Ame, where is Ibyang?
- [Ame] Oh!
We're going home.
Ah, like that. She looks like her.
[sneaky music playing]
That's…
That was… you.
It's her.
You're the woman earlier
at the mall parking lot.
[in English] My love.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
You're really her.
You're her.
You just don't have your mole, but…
I can't be mistaken.
[sneaky music playing]
I can tell, I can never go wrong,
when it comes to my loves.
Ame, what… What are you saying?
Who is this crazy person?
You're being too harsh, calling me crazy.
I'm the one who will be
your future husband slash fiancé.
But you hurt me.
[in English] Straight here, to my heart.
Don't deny it.
I know it's really you. Don't deny it.
You just… your mole in the mall.
Ah, what… how?
Emerson!
Stop it. [grunts] What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Maybe she just looks like the woman.
She's Ibyang's mom!
- Huh?
- This.
Yes.
How could that happen?
I was at a taping all day.
And I don't know you. I just saw you now.
Okay? Please, I'm tired.
Where's Ibyang? Tell her we're going home.
I'll just wait outside.
Okay, I'll call her upstairs.
[sneaky music playing]
[Emerson mutters]
[in English] My love.
- [Karla] It's okay, brother.
- [Ame] Stop it already.
- [in English] How's your heart?
- [Ame] Hey.
[Ame] Ibyang?
OPEN
COME IN!
[in English] My love…
[in English] Someday. Someday.
[music fades]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
Let me see what you're doing.
- [Audrey, in English] Dad.
- [in English] Yes? What?
Um, here's your stuff that they kept
when you were hospitalized.
I already talked to your doctor.
He said you're cleared.
[in English] Wow! Then it's official.
I can travel now.
- [Audrey, in English] Yes!
- [chuckles]
Yay!
Will you come with us, Grandpa?
[in English] Of course!
[in English] Wait, uh…
Where's my ring? It's not here.
[in English] Found it.
[Dmitri] Oh.
[pensive music playing]
[Janine, in English] Mommy.
When are we leaving?
Later, tomorrow?
We'll get your visa first, child.
It's already scheduled,
and once we have that,
we'll buy the ticket.
[in English] Where to?
[in English] Anywhere in the US.
Wherever my grandchild wants to go.
That's where we'll go.
So, where? Where do you
want to go, grandchild?
To Disneyland!
[in English] Sorry.
[chuckles, in English] Disneyland, okay.
[music fades]
[in English] Disneyland it is.
[suspicious music playing]
[Audrey] Janine?
[music swells]
Child?
[in English] Mommy.
- Mommy.
- [in English] Janine, what's wrong?
[in English] Grandchild, are you okay?
Mommy, let's go inside. Please, Mommy?
- Let's go inside, quickly.
- Okay, okay. Let's go.
[in English] Let's go.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[unsettling music playing]
My child.
[hushes]
[in English] It's just
the two of us now, okay?
Child.
What happened?
Why did you cry all of a sudden?
[in English] Tell me.
[in English] What happened?
[music fades]
Mom…
[in English] You look like
you've seen a ghost.
[pensive music playing]
[Mongki] What now?!
[Aldrin] She evaded me.
Didn't you run into her?
No! Where is she?
[music swells]
- Hey! Hey!
- [gunshots]
No one follows!
You thought you could escape from me, huh!
Oh, it's like that, Mommy.
[sniffles]
What do you mean?
Because when I saw
the shoes of Uncle Red's friend,
they were the same shoes
as the one who tried to take me before.
I thought they were going
to take me, Mommy.
I got scared, Mommy.
Janine, don't be scared. Okay?
[in English] You're safe.
[tense music playing]
Where's Dad?
[in English] Mmm, he left. How's Janine?
She's still crying.
She said she suddenly remembered the one
who tried to kidnap her.
[suspicious music playing]
She suddenly remembered? That's weird.
[in English] It's not weird, Red.
The child was traumatized,
and what triggered her…
were your shoes!
Oh? Why my shoes?
There are lots of shoes like that.
Poor child, if she'll always
be triggered by shoes.
[in English] She needs professional help.
Tell me.
Do you know the man
who tried to take my child?
What?
Why are you asking me like that?
Just answer me.
Why would I know him?
I'm not a child trafficker.
[music fades]
Are you sure?
[rousing music playing]
[indicator ticking]
- [Olga] Oh, dear.
- [car door clicks open]
[Olga sighs]
[car door clicks shut]
[footsteps approaching]
Ibyang, what are you doing outside?
Come on. Get inside the car.
Where did you really go earlier?
[suspicious music playing]
In-- Tanay!
What about you?
Why are you talking to me like that, huh?
Gosh, you sound like the parent.
Come on. Let's go.
I'm not going with you.
Why? Are you mad at me?
You're a liar!
It's impossible you're my mom.
You're a scammer!
[music intensifies]
What are you saying?
I'm not a member of the syndicate.
[Red, in English] You know what?
You also need professional help.
Go to therapy.
You're even doubting your family now.
You're too paranoid.
I know the history of this family.
[in English] I just want to make sure.
[music fades]
Prick!
[mysterious music playing]
What was that? The child recognized you.
No!
It was Aldrin
who chased after her back then.
Why did she recognize your shoes?
I don't know.
I don't even remember what I wore then.
I have lots of shoes!
Boss, give us alcohol to relax.
This coffee just made us more nervous.
You know, your sister is just baiting you.
You even said yourself,
Audrey is just paranoid.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm your mother. You're my daughter!
What do you want me to do
so you'll believe me, Ibyang?
Just kidding, Mama!
What? I'm good at acting, right?
[light music playing]
You really are my mom,
- because I take after you.
- Hmm?
Come here.
This is just a secret, okay?
I used to be a scammer too.
Hmm? Really?
Mmm-hmm. Yes.
But when we lived with Tatoy,
I was forbidden to do that
because it's bad.
So, I hope you don't do that anymore.
So, now? What will happen to us?
Nothing!
This is the only job I know.
And it's so hard to land roles
in my career.
So sometimes,
it's unavoidable to do something wrong.
[melancholic music playing]
That's okay.
No one's perfect.
Except for your beauty
and your acting skills.
[Ibyang] It's true!
And I'm sure you'll be famous too.
[in English] Just try and try
until you succeed!
But don't scam people.
Because you might end up in jail.
I want to be with you.
On Christmas, on my birthday.
So many occasions have already passed.
Go on.
Get your things inside.
I'll wait for you here, okay?
Mm-hmm.
[music fades]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[gasps]
[sharp exhale]
Godfather, sorry.
[in Visayan] I got a fright.
[in Visayan] What, Godfather?
[in Visayan] I am inviting you.
[in Visayan] Maybe you wanted
to watch the performance outside.
[in Visayan] Someone might see me.
[in Visayan] I know you're scared
that the ambassador will see you.
[in Visayan] You're safe here.
[in Visayan] I know, Godfather, but…
[in Visayan] Can I stay here?
I feel safer here.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Excuse me, Mayor?
[in Visayan] Should we have
our guests' associates picked up?
Okay.
[music fades]
[sneaky music playing]
[in Visayan] Hey, boss,
my associates are in there.
[in Visayan] I just parked my car.
[in Visayan] You should go and join them.
Yes.
[tires screeching]
[music fades]
[in English] We will proceed as planned.
[in English] But remember,
the decoder must be taken alive.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] We will enter
from the side, but be fast.
[in Russian] Get ready.
[in English] Get ready.
[tense music playing]
Thank you.
[door lock clicks]
[sneaky music playing]
What's this?
[tense music playing]
[in English] What the hell, Red?
[music swells]
[in English] Oh my God.
[music fades]
[Atoy] Sister.
[in Visayan] Where's the bathroom?
[in Visayan] Go through that door,
turn right, and the CR is there.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
- [electronic blipping]
- [tense music playing]
[gunshots]
Sir, they're here, sir!
[armed man on radio]
We're about to catch them, sir!
[thuds]
[thumping and thudding]
UP NEXT
[tranquilizer gunshots]
Dear, maybe you should focus
on Ibyang first.
Make peace with her.
Maybe you're right.
[Olga] The kid isn't doing anything wrong
for me to treat her like that.
This is the first time I've had
such a beautiful doll.
Did I tell you to take this?!
I don't know
how you can stomach doing this?
[Audrey] Even to my own child.
Dad needs to see this.
He knows this. No one will defend you.
[security guard, in English] What are we
going to do with them?
[in English] We have to find out
who he works for.
[security officer, in English]
What if he doesn't talk?
[Samir, in English] Then we will squeeze
this information from them.
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias